Gemini also has a pro option.
So when it comes to Gemini,
the limitations are way lower right now,
and it's way opener to free usage,
then an option like chat GPT.
But Gemini also has a pro option.
So you can click on upgrade to Google AI+ over here as you see.
And let's see what it has for us.
Let's see the priceings, et cetera.
Yes, Google AI Pro, IDR, what is IDR?
I don't get you, and for three months, right?
So you can't let change the currency to see, let's say,
Google AI Pro pricing, just in case I get it
in US dollars, right?
OK, whatever.
It doesn't even matter, because it may change over time.
But whatever.
Yes, AI Pro is, AI+ is actually also possible.